Honest septic
companies win
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
we know everyone
listening to this
right now and I
hope that none of
our listeners are
this person but
we all know not
everyone out
there in the
world is good
people and there
are people who
will go out there
and say that
there's problems
with a system
that there aren't
really problems
or they'll say
you need the
whole system
replaced where
really there's a
repair first that
could be done
rather than a
replacement just
to chase the
bottom dollar
it's kind of like
if you take your
car in and you
don't know
anything about
cars is that
mechanic going to
be truthful and
honest or not so
the same thing is
true with septic
services is that
the more honest
you are you are
going to build
trust